ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.com
■
ShinY
深影
■
ShinY
深影
他在自己房间吗
Is he in his room?
他睡了
He's sleeping.
咱们不要出声
Let's not make any sound.
你刚刚不是说不出声嘛
I thought we weren't making any sound.
你在哪里 你在哪里
Where are you? Where are you?
- 我在这里 - 哦 这里啊
- I'm right here. - Oh, there you are.
翻译
☆Baby Sky★_べo
我教他怎么罚球投篮 他不听
He wouldn't listen to my free throw shooting advice.
翻译
☆Baby Sky★_べo
你这盲人爸爸现在还提供篮球方面的建议啊
You're the blind father giving basketball advice now?
翻译
张写真
对啊
Yes. Yes, I am.
真的吗
Really?
以前我可是全明星球员 知道吗
I used to be quite the all-star player, you know?
翻译
张写真
真的
I was!
我最亲爱的盲人现在感觉怎么样
How's my favorite blind man doing?
眼前还是漆黑一片
Still very much in the dark.
翻译
乖、到碗里来
彼此彼此了
Now we're even.
你给我跳傻瓜舞好不好
Will you do the silly dance for me?
- 不要 - 来嘛
- No. - Please.
- 不要 - 拜托了
- No. - Come on, please.
- 不行 - 来嘛
- No way. - Come on.
你真要我跳吗
You're really gonna make me do it?
我要一直烦到你答应为止
I'm not buying up.
- 真的 - 唉 好吧
- Yeah. - Oh, fine.
翻译
Jasmine夭夭
你现在的样子肯定特别迷人
I bet you look so good right now.
今天鲍勃给我讲了一个故事
Oh, Bob told me a story today.
亲爱的 我明天还要早起
Honey,I have to get up early tomorrow.
好吧 那我就不讲给你听了
Fine.Okay.I won't tell you.
不过这故事很棒呢
It's a good story, though.
好吧 你说吧
Okay, fine. Let's hear it.
好
Hmm. All right, so...
有个人
There's this man...
他特别想中彩票
And he really wants to win the lottery.
所以他就向上帝祈祷
So, he prays to god.
翻译
A.I.
五十年来 每天都祈祷
Every night for 50 years.
夜复一夜 他祈祷不停
Night, after night, after night, he prays.
翻译
A.I.
"求你了 上帝 让我中彩票吧"
"Please god, please, let me win the lottery."
最后
And finally,
一个天使去跟上帝说
an angel goes to god, and he says,
"上帝 我们就让这人中一次彩票吧"
"God, why don't we let this guy win?"
你知道上帝说什么吗
And you know what god says?
什么
What?
上帝说
God says,
"我也想啊
"I want to...
但他从没买过彩票啊"
But he's never bought a lottery ticket."
校对
羊舌
- 哦 - 看吧
- Oh. - You see?
- 故事不错吧 - 嗯 是不错
- It was a good story. - Yeah, it's all right.
校对
羊舌
特效
TTTYM
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
特效
TTTYM
压制
LUCIA
亲爱的上帝 我感恩自己拥有的一切
Dear god, I'm thankful for everything I have.
我对我的生活和经历都很满足
I am deeply satisfied with my life and everything in it.
我为今天而活 我享受每一天
And I live for today, and I enjoy what I do.
我不与他人攀比
I do not compare myself to others.
爸爸
Dad?
怎么了 儿子
Yeah, son.
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
嗯 没事
Yeah. Yeah, of course it is.
只是出来透透气
I was just getting some air.
好了 我们进去吧
Here, let's go back inside.
你明天还得上学呢 走吧
You have school tomorrow. Come on.
我的天
Oh, my god.
亲爱的
Honey?
你怎么了
What's wrong?
- 我...我能看见你了 - 什么
- I...I can see you. - Huh?
我能看见你了
I can see you.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
怎么会
How?
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
我不...我也不...
I don't... I don't...
垂体肿瘤怎么会
how can a pituitary tumor
一夜之间就消失呢
just disappear overnight?
没有消失 只是缩小了
It didn't disappear, it shrank.
虽然罕见 但也不是前所未有
It is rare, but not unheard of.
不过好消息是它正在挤压
But the good news is it's normally pushing up
视神经交叉
against the optic chiasm.
所以他才能看见的吗
Which is how he can see?
先让他留院观察几天
We'll only keep him here for a few days.
我们要确保不会出现令人担忧的情况
We just wanna make sure there isn't cause for concern.
所以他得住院吗
So, you need to admit him?
只要几天就行了
Just for a few days.
欢迎回家
Welcome home!
他们带乔出去了
They're brushing Joan out.
对了 我给你们公司打过电话了 跟鲍勃说了
Oh, and I called your work, talked to Bob.
他会告诉公司的人
He's gonna talk to them.
人力资源部说你想休息多久都行
And HR told you to take as much time as you need.
不用着急回去上班
And they're fine with you not coming in
等你好些了再去 所以...
until you feel up for it. So, um...
对了 我来把它拉开
Here, let me get that.
我可以自己来
I can do that.
我知道
Oh, I know.
我去给公司打个电话
I'm just gonna call work
就说我生病了
and tell them that I'm not feeling well.
得在家休息
Stay home.
我得弄一下头发
I need to do something with my hair.
毕竟你能看见我了
Now that you can see me.
我都不知道现在该做什么了
I have no idea what to do now.
我去做午饭 好吗
I'll go make us some lunch. Okay?
我没事的
I'll... I'll be fine.
知道吗
You know?
- 我没事的 - 我知道
- I'll be fine. - Yeah, I know.
我没事了
Here I am.
太不可思议了
This is crazy.
是啊
I know.
我花了半小时才找到这里
Took me 30 minutes to find that place.
疼吗
Does it hurt?
不疼
No. Nah.
一点也不疼
No, not at all.
医生怎么说
What did the doctor say?
医生
He...
也不知道怎么回事
couldn't explain it.
所以 这是个奇迹
So, it's a miracle?
也可以这么说
Well, you could say that.
不打算解释一下你的脸怎么了吗
Are you gonna tell me what happened to your face?
妈妈叫我别告诉你
Mom said not to tell you.
她...看见你的伤了
She... she saw this?
她中午来过
She came at lunch.
学校给她打电话了
They called her from school.
发生什么事了
What happened?
就是打了一架 没什么的
Got into a fight. It's not a big deal.
谁打的
Well, who gave it to ya?
别管了
Don't worry about it.
乔纳
Jonah...
妈妈说她会处理的
mom... mom said she'll take care of it.
乔纳 是谁打的
Jonah, who gave it to you?
你不用担心
You don't need to worry about it.
谁这么说的
Who told you that?
我只是不想你期望越大
I just don't want you to expect too much
失望越大
and be disappointed.
我为什么会失望呢
Why would I be disappointed?
看起来有点寒酸
It's a little sad-looking.
走吧
Come on.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
是不是很不可思议
Do you believe this?
等一下 我去把包放下
Hang on. Let me put my bag down.
来吧
Come on.
说点什么啊 你觉得怎么样
Well, say something. What do you think?
这种感觉太陌生了
This is so strange.
我明白
I know.
我想看傻瓜舞
Aw, I want to see the silly dance.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你的表演
Thank you.
我们的生活会更好的
We're gonna have a better life now.
现在已经很好了
We already do.
不只是我的眼睛变好了
Not just my eyes.
一切都会更好的
Everything.
即便只是你恢复了视力 我也很满足了
Even if it is just your eyes.
我会升职
I'm gonna get that promotion.
我们可以去度假
We can go on vacation.
买个大房子
We can get a bigger house.
我喜欢这个房子
I like our house.
买个有大院子的房子
One with a big backyard.
陪你逛街
Take you shopping.
欢迎致电千禧房产
Thank you for calling millennium realty...
请问您需要什么帮助
How can I help you?
他们说关键是 在非洲
They say the point is, in Africa,
太阳一出
when the sun comes up,
你最好赶紧逃吧
you'd better be running.
下午好 我是罗布·布雪
Good afternoon, this is Rob Boucher
这里是千禧房产有限公司
from the millennium real estate corporation.
请问内波利女士在家吗
Is Ms. Nepoli at home, please?
太好了 我只是想确认一下...
Oh, good. I just want to make sure...
你能相信吗
Can you believe this?
那人做我们这份工作时
When that guy was sitting at this desk,
他一笔生意都没做成
he didn't move a single house.
我来公司时间比他久
I've been here longer.
谈成的房子比他多得多
I've put many more houses on the board.
为什么当老板的是他
Why is he the boss?
说真的 一个简单的问题
No, seriously. A simple question.
那家伙做这工作时 表现可不怎么样
When that guy was sitting here, he didn't do squat.
- 对吧 - 鲍勃
- Okay? - Bob.
喂
Hello?
我是詹姆斯·哈维
My name is James Harvey,
这里是千禧房产...
I'm calling from millennium realty...
今天怎么样 迪克森先生
How are you doing today, Mr. Dixon?
不错 鲍勃 你好
Fine, Bob, how are you?
你工作做得不错
You're doing a great job.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 真的很不错 - 你也是
- Really great. - You, too.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我能自己住一间房吗
Am I gonna get my own room?
不行
Nope.
我们已经预约好了
We have a reservation.
我脸上还有防晒霜吗
Have any cream on my face?
没了 抹得很均匀
No, you're good.
好的
Okay.
- 帮我拿一下好吗 - 好啊
- Can you hold this? - Sure.
一起吗
Comin'?
来嘛
Come on!
多漂亮啊
It's beautiful.
你在里面干嘛呢
What are you doing in there?
别没玩没了地照镜子了
Stop spending time in front of the mirror.
嘿
Hey.
# 噢 我试过了#
# Oh, I've tried #
# 许久以来 #
# for a long, long time #
# 寻找着意中人 #
# tried to find a guy #
# 我的意中人 #
# that I could call mine #
# 好男人啊 我的宝贝 宝贝 #
# a good man, my baby,my baby  #
# 可遇不可求 #
# is so very hard to find #
# 爱需要有所寄托 #
# need someone to love #
# 放轻松 #
# I relax  #
# 假装自己很快乐 #
# and act like the happy girl  #
我还从没见过这些
I've never seen anything like this.
你不常度假的吧
You don't vacation much.
我几乎没什么常做的事情
I don't do much of anything.
这虽然看起来不怎么样 但感觉起来很棒
It's one of those things that feels better than it looks.
我想我明白你的意思
I think I know what you mean.
# 爱需要有所寄托 #
# Need someone to love #
我跟我妻子和孩子一起来的
I'm here with my wife and son.
我跟我丈夫一起来的
I'm here with my husband.
我得上楼去看看他们怎么样了
I should probably go check on them upstairs.
# 我会等待 一直等待 #
# But I've waited, yes, I've waited #
# 我的内心真的真的好孤独 #
# So very, very, very alone inside me #
# 有时候 我想啊想 #
# sometimes I wonder #
# sometimes I wonder  #
能邀请你跳一支舞吗
Would you like to dance with me?
当然
Sure.
# 邂逅 #
# Come our way #
# 终有一天 我将知晓 #
# one day I will know #
# 愿望可否成真 #
# if my wish will come true #
# 我将寻得一个好男人 #
# I'm gonna find a good man to love #
# 像你这样的男人 #
# just like you #
# 但愿能成真 #
# I hope it's real, so, yes, I do #
# 在那之前 #
# but until I do #
# 爱需要有所寄托 #
# need someone to love #
# 我明白 明白 姑娘 #
# oh, I know, I know,I know, girl  #
# 爱需要有所寄托 #
# need someone to love #
我先送你们回家
I'll drop you guys off at home
然后开车去买点东西
and take the car and go grocery shopping.
天哪 我真不想回去工作
Oh, man, I do not feel like going back to work.
真希望我们能在那里度过余生
I wish we could just stay there for the rest of our lives.
那会很棒的 是不是
It would be nice, wouldn't it?
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
什么
What?
乔纳以前打过架吗
Did Jonah ever get in fights before?
以前是什么意思
What do you mean before?
你懂的 就今年
You know, this year.
他十三岁了
He's 13.
这个年纪的孩子总是打架
They get into fights all the time.
我指的是很严重的那种
I mean, serious fights.
亲爱的...
Honey...
打出熊猫眼之类的 你从没告诉过我
Black eyes and stuff. You never told me.
没那么糟糕 没有的事
Never that bad. No.
现在是上午八点零四分
It is 8:04 A.M.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你好 我是詹姆斯·哈维 这里是...
Hello, my name is James Harvey, and I'm calling from...
⁮下午好 我是罗伯特·布雪
good afternoon, this is Robert boucher.
阿博特先生 这里是千禧房产公司...
Mr. Abbott, I'm calling from millennium realty...
我想也许...
I was just wondering if, uh...
您收到过我们的邮件
You might have seen a mailer from us.
或许我们应该从整个市场入手
Maybe we have to start with the market as a whole.
等一下
Just give me a second.
您好
Hello.
翁贝托先生
Mr. Umberto,
我是千禧房产的詹姆斯·哈维
it's James Harvey, millennium realty.
我致电是为了告诉您
Yes, I wanted to call and let you know
接下来几个月
that in the next few months
你们小区的十来套房子的赎取权
about a dozen houses in your neighborhood
将被取消
are gonna be foreclosed.
一旦银行取消了赎取权
And once the bank forecloses those houses,
整个街区的产权价值就会下跌
the overall property value for the block goes down.
很快 您现在的房产就不再值钱了
Pretty soon what you had, what you have now, isn't worth much.
用这几张卡分开付
Split it between these.
所以我打算为您提供一份交易
So, I'm calling you today with an offer.
我们的报价不会特别高 但价格公正
It's not going to knock you off your feet, but it's fair.
很划算 我们还会帮您找到新住所
It's fair, and it will help you find another place to live.
好 那我们开始吧 您能记一下号码吗
So, let's start by doing this, can you write a number down?
我给您我的私人号码
I'm gonna give you my personal number.
不是公司的分机
This is not a company extension.
我也不是在印度
I'm not calling you from India.
您可以随时来电
You can call me anytime,
整个过程我都会帮您
I'll be with you through this process.
我为您负责 为您服务
I'm your point man, I'm your guy.
现在 翁贝托先生 唯一剩下的问题是...
Now, the only question that remains, Mr. Umberto, is...
您身边有笔吗
Do you have a pen?
谢谢
Thank you.
所以呢
So...
我昨晚约会了
I went on a date last night.
是吗
Really?
和谁啊
With who? Well...
怎么约上的
How'd you meet?
你都没告诉我们
You didn't tell us.
她很不错 她...
She was great, you know? She's...
很聪明
smart.
体贴 周到
Attentive, thoughtful.
但是偏胖
But on the heavy side.
真好啊 鲍勃
That's great, Bob.
偏胖 你真的对她有意思吗
Bit on the heavy side? You think it's serious?
什么意思
What's that mean?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么不
Why not?
我们小小争论了一番
We had, uh, a little argument.
她说她宁可变聋也不愿变瞎
You know, she said she'd rather be deaf than blind.
天哪 鲍勃 你和女人在一起的时候
Oh, Bob, can't you sit with a woman for five minutes
就不能别提这个吗
without bringing that one up?
该死的 你问她那问题了
Oh, damn, do you ask her that?
交流很重要的 好吗
It's really about communicating, you know?
我的意思是 想一想... 音乐很重要
I mean, think about... think about music.
这顿饭很重要 天哪
The meal is important. Oh, boy.
嘿 是不是得有人代表发言
Hey. Somebody gotta represent.
毕竟你抛弃我们了
Now that you deserted us.
谁抛弃谁了
Who deserted who?
鲍勃 我没有抛弃你 我还在公司的啊
Bob, I didn't desert you. I'm still there.
嗯 当然在
Hmm, sure are.
你听说了你丈夫的新职业道德吗
Hear about your husband's new-found work ethic?
他现在可是办公室之星
He's the star of the office.
真的吗
Really?
你做了多少单生意啊 老爸
How many deals did you make, dad?
乔纳 远远不够
Jonah! Not enough.
说吧 詹姆斯
Come on, James.
我们比比赛吧
Let's get a little competition goin'.
是啊 快说吧 爸爸 多少笔
Yeah, come on, dad. How many?
- 爸爸 - 快啊
- Dad? - Come on.
- 各位 吃馅饼吧好吗 - 你和我
- Guys, please dig into the pie. - You and me.
馅饼要凉了
It's going to get cold.
大概三笔吧
About three.
爸爸
Oh, come on, dad.
你得说具体点
You have to be specific.
多少啊
How many?
你把那个放哪儿了
Where did you put the...?
没事儿了 我找着了
Oh, never mind, I found it.
- 多少啊 - 乔纳 别问了
- How many? - Jonah, stop it.
说吧 我想知道
Come on, I wanna know.
多少啊 你做成了几笔啊
How many? How many deals you make?
我们别在吃饭时聊工作 行吗
Can we not talk about work at the dinner table?
谢谢你们
Thank you!
有人要咖啡或茶吗
Oh, who wants coffee or tea?
来吃馅饼吧
Come eat your pie.
过来
Come here.
- 什么 - 过来
- What? - Come here.
我想给你看个东西
I want to show you something.
过来 过来
Come here. Come here.
看到没
You see it?
看到了吗
See?
咦
Yeah?
我升职了
I got the promotion.
我不想在他面前说 周一他就会知道的
I didn't want to say anything in front of him, he'll know Monday.
- 太棒了 - 你喜欢吗
- That's great. - You like it?
怎么了
What's the matter?
你都没告诉我
You didn't tell me!
我只是想给你个惊喜
Oh, I wanted it to be a surprise.
你不高兴吗
Aren't you happy?
高兴啊 当然高兴
Yeah! Of course.
差不多成倍的单子
It's almost double.
他们知道你不会开车吗
Do they know you can't drive?
我会学的
I'm gonna learn.
- 我只是担心你伤到自己 - 萨姆
- I'm just worried you'll hurt yourself. - Sam.
不 我们并不清楚 万一你...
No, we don't know anything. What if you...
开车时又看不见了怎么办
Lose it while you're driving?
你想让我怎么办 你想让我坐着干等吗
What do you want me to do? You want me to sit and wait?
你该为我高兴的
You should be happy.
我是很高兴
I am happy.
别这么担心
Don't worry so much.
我只是害怕 你明白吗
I'm just scared, you know?
你不想失去你的主控权
You don't wanna lose control.
不是这样的
That's not true.
你怎么会这么想
Why would you say that?
你们还好吗
Everything okay in here?
挺好的 鲍勃 我送你回去
Yeah. Bob, let me, uh, let me drive you home.
你从哪儿弄来这些东西啊
Where do you get all this from?
我们去哪儿
Where are we going?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything!
哈维先生...
Mr. Harvey...
他和比利·傅利打架 你不能每次
you can't blame Jonah every time he and Billy forley
都责备乔纳 我不会容忍这种事
get in a fight, I will not stand for it.
你不能不讲公正 惩罚我儿子
You will not punish my son unjustly.
其他三个学生都说是你儿子先动手的
I have three other students who say your son started it.
他们都是比利的朋友
Those are all Billy's friends.
哈维先生 别闯进我的办公室
Mr. Harvey, don't barge into my office
教我怎么管理学校
and tell me how to run my school.
好啊
Fine.
我不会教你怎么管理学校
I won't tell you how to run it,
但你也别想因为他人的过错
but you don't punish my son
而惩罚我儿子
when he isn't responsible for the problem.
你太酷了
That was awesome.
走 我们离开这儿
Come on, let's get out of here.
我有五堂课
I have fifth period.
走吧
Ah, come on.
- 真的吗 - 是啊 我们走
- Really? - Yeah, let's go.
哎呀 不见了
Oh, now he's gone.
慢慢移动
Move really slow.
这儿有一条
Hey, there's one.
有吗 啊没错
Is that one? Oh, yeah.
他把半个身子都藏在石头下面了
He's curled like half underneath the rock.
他去哪儿了
Where'd he go?
看看这边
Let's look up under here.
- 看到了吗 - 没有
- See any? - No.
有条鱼
But there's a fish, though.
哪儿
Where?
那里 在那儿
There. There he is.
对啊
Oh, yeah.
可能这边更多
Maybe more up here?
可能在那里呢
Maybe over there.
知道吗 你可以不回那所学校
You know, you don't have to go back there
如果你不愿意的话
if you don't want to.
我们可以送你去其他学校
We can send you someplace else.
比如私立学校
You know, private school.
我们付不起学费的
We can't afford it.
这个我来想办法
You let me worry about that.
但是谁想呢
Who wants to, anyway?
你以为伍德兰就没有比利·傅利之流了吗
You think there's no Billy Forleys at woodland?
至少那里的恶霸衣冠楚楚
At least the bullies there will be better dressed.
没事的 爸爸
It's okay, dad.
我能熬过去的
I'm gonna tough it out.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
你打算忍忍就过去了 是吗
Oh, you wanna tough it out, do ya?
忍忍就过去了吗
Wanna tough it out?
忍忍就过去了对吗
You wanna tough it out?
是啊
Oh, yeah!
打住
Stop!
在地产成交会 25个资助
25 funded at closing,
一个在蒙哥马利的
for the development
五十套房的住宅区项目
of a 50-home residential neighborhood project
的发展
in Montgomery county.
首笔抵押贷款的额度
The first mortgage loan represents an underwritten
约为净出售额的百分之68
loan to net sellout of approximately 68 percent.
保证内部收益率
And has been underwritten to generate an irr
达到大概...
of approximately...
百分之五
five percent.
我们催得还不够
We're not pushing hard enough.
我们可以增加市场开销
We can increase marketing spend.
在每个街区发传单
We flyer every block.
挨家挨户敲门 打电话推销
We go door to door. We... cold call.
我们在每个社区都设了地方办公室
We have a local office for each community.
但这些我们都已经做过了
But we've already been doing all of that.
我们可以增加工作量
We can do more.
问题不在于接触顾客
The problem isn't getting to people.
他们知道我们的存在
People know we're out there.
但我们知道问题在哪儿
But we know what the problem is.
在于信任
The problem is trust.
人们认为这是一家冷血的房地产公司
People think we're a cold- blooded real estate company.
那是好事 不是吗
That's a good thing, right?
我只是告诉你们 过去七年里
I'm just telling you what I've been hearing
我打了那么多电话
for the past seven years...
了解到的情况
Working the phones.
我们并不比富兰克林或霍华德房地产
We're no more cold-blooded than Franklin and Howard
或其他公司更冷血
or any of the others.
没错 他们也在拼呢
That's right, and they're all struggling, too.
我们需要重新定位我们的品牌
We need to reposition our brand.
变成好公司
Become the good guys.
我以为我们本来就是呢
I thought we are the good guys.
那你有什么建议
Oh, what are you suggesting?
组织慈善活动吗
You want to start a charity?
这主意会很糟吗
Would that be so bad?
听着 我讨厌不得不去...
Listen, I hate having to...
别担心 我会解决的
Oh, don't worry. I'll take care of it.
如果他们拒绝了呢
What if they say no?
你真觉得会发生吗
Are you really asking me that?
好吧 那我叫他等着你
Okay, so I'll tell him to expect you.
对 就这样吧
Yeah, you do that.
新晋金童想干什么呢
And what does the golden boy want?
吃午餐
Lunch.
我不吃午餐
Oh, I don't lunch.
和我共进午餐呢
Lunch with me?
给个理由
Why should I?
我想跟你谈谈
I wanna talk about this.
谈什么
This what?
这次挑战
This challenge.
你想分享主意吗
You wanna share ideas?
对
I do.
为什么
Why?
我... 需要你帮忙
I... could use your help.
我为什么要帮你
And why should I help you?
我觉得你能借鉴一下我的视角
I think you could use my perspective.
小金童 你只不过买卖了几个房子
Golden boy, you just flipped a couple of houses,
升了职而已
got yourself promoted.
别得意忘形
Don't let it go to your head.
我不明白为什么我们要来这里
I don't see why we had to come here.
我想带你出来吃饭
I wanted to take you out.
跳舞不好吗
What's wrong with dancing?
好吧 我们去跳舞 等我先结账
Sure, we'll go dancing. Let me get the check.
不 不 不 不用了
No, no, no. It's fine.
萨姆
Sam.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你在乔纳学校里做的事 我知道了
I heard what you did at Jonah's school.
孩子需要放松一下
The kid needed a break.
好吧...
Well...
我给老师打电话了 让他留堂了
I called them and told them to give him detention.
什么
You what?
他不能逃课 而且...
He can't cut class and...
是我允许的啊
I gave him my permission.
你没权利那么做
You don't get to do that!
为什么没有
Why not?
因为你没权利替我们两个
Because you don't get to make the decision
做决定
for both of us!
真的吗
Really?
因为你以前从没告诉过我
Because you never used to tell me
他在学校里被欺负
when he got in trouble at school.
我不想让你为此心烦
I didn't want to bother you with that.
好吧 但是现在我知道了
Well, now I know.
你这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
现在我知道了
Now I know.
我不喜欢这里
I don't like this.
那我们去跳舞吧
Let's go dancing.
- 我不想去 - 走吧 走吧
- I don't want to. - No, let's go.
走吧 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
詹姆斯...
James...
我们重新开始
We'll start over.
继续说
Go ahead.
大家都知道市场不景气
Everyone knows the market is bad.
您家的钟点工都知道市场不景气
The woman cleaning your house knows the market is bad.
人们都觉得
People tell themselves,
"现在卖掉房子的话就太蠢了"
"I'd have to be an idiot to sell now."
所以 我们成立一个独立的顾问部门
So, we establish a separate consulting entity.
在学校 社区中心 教堂举办活动
We hold meetings in schools, community centers, churches.
帮助人们管理债务
We help people manage debt.
提供我们的解决方案
And we offer our own solution.
有了教堂的参与 人们就会参加活动
People will show up just because it's church.
还有关于家庭理财的夜校
Evening classes in family finance.
他们会蜂拥而来
They'll come in droves.
我们将提供 解决债务问题的整体规划
What we offer, a comprehensive plan for solving debt,
整合收入 做家庭预算
consolidating, making a family budget,
先偿还小额债务
paying off small debts first.
作为我们推销的解决方案之一
One of the solutions we'll be selling.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得他挺有道理
I think he's got a point.
今天差点就谈成一笔了
So close to one today.
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道吗 就那一瞬间
You know, that split...
他们就在签字前
that split-second where they're not sure
那一瞬间犹豫了
if they're gonna sign on the dotted line or not.
功亏一篑啊
I blew it.
我都干了什么
I don't know.
我想我有点走神了
I think my mind wandered a little bit.
你怎么收尾的
How do you close?
- 我怎么收尾的 - 对
- How do you close? - Yeah.
就看着对方的眼睛
You look the guy right in the eye.
然后说 "你愿意这样做吗"
And you say, "Are you willing to do this?"
爸爸
Hey, dad.
你怎么还没睡
What are you doin' up?
妈妈说你去派对了 没带她
Mom said you went to a party and didn't take her.
去睡吧
Go to bed.
派对怎么样
How was it?
还行
Fine.
玩得开心吗
Have fun?
你跟乔纳说我不让你去
You told Jonah I didn't want you to come
但是我...我问过你了啊
but I...I did ask you.
那不重要
Doesn't matter.
我能问你点事吗
Can I ask you something?
我们初次见面的时候
That first time we met.
在社区中心的舞会
At the dance at the community center.
怎么了
What about it?
为什么是我 你为什么...
Why me? Why did you...?
你为什么选了我
Why did you choose me?
你一脸怏怏不乐
You looked unhappy.
我想着我能帮你
I thought I could help.
通常 你邀请别人跳舞
Well, usually, when you ask someone to dance,
是因为他们吸引了你
it's because you're attracted to them.
当时你看上去惨兮兮的
Well, you looked miserable out there.
我们就是惨兮兮的盲人...
We're the sorry-looking group of blind people...
坐在寒酸的社区中心里
in the sorry-looking community center.
你同情我
You pitied me.
不是的 我没有
No, I didn't.
在那个盲人派对上 你可怜我
You pitied me at the party for the blind.
你同情我 然后你选了我
You pitied me, and you took me on,
就像对待你学校里的那些孩子
like one of those kids at your school.
做帮扶项目
Project.
别说了
Stop it.
同情的目光
Pitiful sight.
明天我会去跳舞 因为我答应过你了
I'll go dancing tomorrow because I promised.
但以后我不会再去了
But I'm never going there again.
# 哦宝贝 #
# Ooh, baby #
# 当我们月下漫步 #
# when we're out in the moonlight #
# 望着满天繁星 #
# looking up on stars above #
# 与你相依 感觉如此美妙 #
# feels so good when I'm near you #
# 紧握双手 让爱意蔓延 #
# holding hands and making love #
# 哦宝贝 #
# ooh, ooh, baby #
# 沙滩上 你侬我侬 #
# Sandy beach and was making love #
# 海浪拍打在我们身上 #
# as the tide moves in on us #
# 并肩而行 感觉如此美妙 #
# feels so good walking side by side #
# 多想和你共度此生 #
# want to be with you all my life #
# 哦宝贝 #
# ooh, ooh, baby #
# 啊 宝贝 #
# yes, oh, baby #
# 哦 宝贝 #
# 思君忆君 魂牵梦萦 #
# dreams of you all the time #
# 相守如此美妙 爱啊 #
# feels so good when we're together, love #
# 连明晚都等不及 #
# just can't wait until tomorrow night #
如果你选择离开 没有回头路可走
If you leave, you can't come back.
你知道的 对吧
You know that, right?
你要带我去哪儿
Where are you taking me?
走 我带你去看看湖
Come on, I'll show you the water.
所以...
So...
这就是你住的地方
Yeah, of course, this is where you live.
以前我在电梯里闻着你的香水味
I used to smell your perfume in the elevator.
你知道吗
Do you know that?
每天早上都能闻到
Every morning.
人们希望有人能告诉他们
People are looking for someone to tell them
如何摆脱债务
how to get out of debt.
这是他们急需的
They're starving for this stuff.
对 但为什么选这里
Yeah, but why here?
人在困难时期还会去哪儿呢
Where else do people go in hard times?
我们...我们就是想提供帮助
We...we really just want to help.
鲍勃会主持这些活动
Bob will be leading these meetings.
现在 我们主要希望你们能
Now, primarily we want you
把我们当做信息来源
to see us as a source of information.
你们可以向我们咨询任何问题
And we want you to ask us any question at all.
没有任何禁区
Nothing is off bounds.
绝对没有
Absolutely nothing.
我们也希望你们了解 我们可以为你们
Um, we also want you to know that we can refer you to...
提供金融服务
Uh, financial services.
当作万不得已时的选择
Just purely as a last resort,
以防你们想重新为房产估值
in case you want to have, uh, your house reevaluated.
我觉得...
I think that...
这个小册子上就有具体的金额
I'm pretty sure there's a number on this pamphlet.
现在 我想向大家介绍我在旭日联众中的
Now, I'd like to introduce a dear friend and partner
一位密友和搭档
in New Day Alliance,
詹姆斯·哈维
James Harvey.
干得漂亮 鲍勃
Good job, Bob.
台阶在这
You want to step here.
自己可以吗
You good?
谢谢鲍勃
Thank you, Bob!
也谢谢大家今天的捧场
And thank you all for being here.
有一个人...
A man...
向上帝祈祷了
prays to god...
五十年
for 50 years.
每晚重复同样的祷告
The same prayer, every night.
上帝啊...
God...
让我中一次彩票吧
please let me win the lottery.
每天晚上 年复一年 祈祷不停
Every night, year after year, after year, after year.
"求你了 上帝
"Please...god...
让我中一次大奖吧"
Let me win the lottery."
终于有一个天使问上帝
And finally an angel goes to god.
他说 "上帝
And he says, "God...
这个人祈祷了这么久
This man has been praying so long.
您为什么不让他中一次呢"
Why don't you let him win? "
你们猜上帝怎么说
And you know what god says?
上帝说 "我也想让他中啊
God says, "I'd love to help him out.
乐意之至
Love to help him out.
但他从没买过彩票啊"
But he's never bought a lottery ticket!"
现在 我看着你们 看到了不同的面孔
Now, I look into this crowd, and I see different faces.
有老人
I see old men and women.
也有年轻夫妻
I see young couples.
还有单身妈妈
Single mothers.
年轻小伙子
Young men.
还有一家人
Whole families.
你们为什么都来到了这里 为什么
Why are you all here? Why are you all here?
因为你们的沉溺
It's because of your addiction.
你们沉溺于债务
Your addiction to debt.
沉溺于债务经济
To the economy of debt.
从来不接那个陌生号码
To never picking up when that unlisted number
打来的电话
flashes on your phone.
每天一睁眼就躲避催债电话
To waking up in the morning and dodging phone calls.
和银行账单
And red letters.
最终
And finally,
在家里不开灯 就不会有人来催债
to sitting at home in the dark so you can't get served.
然后开始祈祷
So we go, and we pray.
哭泣
And we cry.
自悲自怜
And we feel sorry for ourselves.
为什么呢 为什么我们会那样做
And why? Why do we do that?
因为我们没有采取行动的勇气
It's because we don't have the guts to take action.
去摆脱债务
To get out of debt.
卖掉汽车
To sell that car.
换个小点的房子
To move to a smaller house.
买那张彩票
To get that ticket.
我们负债是因为找不到工作
We got debt because we can't get jobs.
看 连借口都想好了
So we come up with excuses.
"我找不到工作"
"I can't get a job."
"我赚的太少 收入太低"
"I make too little, the money is too low."
"我举步维艰"
"I can't move ahead."
是... 也许你说得对
And... and maybe that's right.
你寸步难行 收入太低
"I make too little, the money is too low."
我们都会遇到这些问题 对吗
I mean, we all have these problems, right?
我们都有这些问题
We all have these problems.
那为何我们还理所当然地超前消费呢
Then, why do we feel it right to live beyond our means?
为何要过入不敷出的生活
Why should we live beyond our earnings?
十五年来 我们被牢牢困住
What sense does it make when we're stuck,
债务缠身
15 years down the line,
这么做意义何在
shackled with debt?
债务压得我们喘不过气
Debt hanging down our throats.
银行在乎你生活艰难吗
Does the bank care about your hard life?
- 不 - 不会
- No. - No.
在乎你收入低下吗
Do they care about your low income?
不 他们不在乎
No. No, they don't!
他们不在乎
No, they don't!
升职了很高兴吧
So are you enjoying the promotion?
我想我们能帮人们走出困境
I guess we can help these people out, you know?
你知道吗 如果这件事做好了
You know, if this keeps up,
我肯定能再给你加薪
I can definitely get you another raise.
也许给你一间独立办公室
Maybe your own office?
新公寓怎么样
How's the new apartment?
很棒
Uh, it's... it's great.
你有空应该过来坐坐
Hey, you should come by sometime.
感觉如何
What's it like?
什么
What?
和她在一起
With her.
和她那什么感觉如何
What's it like with her?
鲍勃 我觉得自己不想...
Bob, I don't know if I want to...
说呀
Come on.
她做了什么 有没有给你来点特殊花样
What does she do? She do anything special for ya?
来啊 说说 快跟我说说
Come on. Tell... tell... tell me something.
她挺不错的
She's good.
挺不错的
It's good.
最好是 最好是不错
Better be. It better be good.
我去看过萨姆了
I've been, uh, over to see Sam.
哦是吗 为什么
Oh, yeah? How come?
我也是她的朋友
Um... um, I'm her friend, too.
不是吗 我是说 她...已经够艰难的了
Right? I mean, she... she had it hard enough.
哦 我明白 明白
Oh, I know. I know.
詹姆斯 我不是评判你 不是说你什么
James, I'm not judging. I'm not judging.
嗯不是 当然不是
Oh, no, of course not.
不 说得好像如果你有这机会
No. Like you wouldn't have done the same thing
不会像我这么做一样
if you had the chance.
什么机会
What chance?
哦拜托 还需要我说出来吗
Oh, please. I need... I need to spell it out?
对
Yeah.
是的 说出来 你用盲文给我说出来
Yes, spell it out. Spell it out in braille for me.
得到你想要的东西的机会
The chance to get what you want.
历经多年悲惨 终于有所成就的机会
To finally go somewhere after years of misery.
我不觉得过去有多糟糕
I didn't realize that things were so bad.
过去当你还看不见的时候
When you were like me.
哦 我不是那个意思
Oh, I didn't mean that.
不是吗
No?
你知道吗 很多人比盲人惨多了
A lot of people have it a lot worse, you know?
鲍勃 你才是那个一直抱怨的人
Bob, you were the one who would always complain.
"这家伙升职了 为什么不是我"
"Hmm, this guy got promoted, why not me?"
"我...我都在这工作这么久了"
"I've... I've been here forever."
"我做得比任何人都好"
"I'm better at this than everybody else."
但我觉得 就算有那机会
I don't know if I would've been planning
我也不会想着抛弃家人
to leave my family, though.
抛妻弃子应该不在
That might not have been part of my plan,
我的计划之内
leaving the family.
听着 你讲的那个故事...
Listen, that story you told me...
关于彩票的
The ticket.
我得到了机会 我抓住机遇 我成功了
I got a chance. I reached out, and I got it.
你没抓到这故事的重点
You missed the point of the story.
哦 是吗
Oh, am I?
是的 你从没得到那张彩票
Yeah, yeah, you never got a ticket.
只不过暂时传给你
You had one handed to you.
暂时传到你手上罢了
You had a ticket handed to you.
所以你在问"为什么不是我" 对吧
So, you're asking, "Why not me"? Hmm?
也许我在问 "你凭什么得到它"
Maybe I'm asking, "What did you do to deserve it?"
你嫉妒了
You're jealous.
你这是嫉妒
You are jealous.
而你成了个混蛋
And you're being an asshole.
我只是遵循人性
I'm human.
鲍勃
Bob.
原来如此 好的
That's what it is. Okay.
明白了
Got it.
提醒一下 我买了单了
In case you didn't hear that, I just paid.
你最近感觉如何
How have you been feeling?
你的表现十分瞩目
Your performance doesn't go unnoticed.
你付出的这些努力
The effort you're putting in.
这些成果
The results.
很高兴能有所贡献
Feels good to contribute.
我知道你想听我说什么
I know what you want to hear.
说我们要扩大项目
That we're going to expand the program,
就得有项目负责人
someone will have to run it,
掌握实权 组建团队
get a substantial promotion, find the right staff.
你的确是我的头号人选
You'd be my first choice.
谢谢
Thank you.
这件事是我们的当务之急
And this is probably the first order of business.
今早在我的挡风玻璃上看到的
I found this on my windshield this morning.
这事不能掉以轻心 绝对不行
Not something we wanna take lightly. Not now.
我会谨慎处理的
I'll take care of it.
尽快吗
As quickly as you can?
好的 我们得谈一谈
Sure. We need to talk.
是我
It's me.
我知道
I know.
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
- 做什么 - 哦拜托 鲍勃
- Doin' what? - Oh, come on, Bob!
你为什么对我做出这种事
Why are you doing this to me, huh?
这不是针对你 詹姆斯
Not really about you, James.
是为了那些被我们踩在脚底的人
It's all those people we're stepping on.
得了吧 别假装你怜悯他们
Oh, don't pretend this is about the people.
你很久以前就在打电话
You were making phone calls screwing people over
坑他们了啊
well before any of this!
我们的差别就是 你表现拙劣
Only difference is you sucked at it!
不 这是你我之间的事
No, this is about you and me and your inability
因为你无能跟上我的步伐
to cope with where I'm going!
的确 是你一个人对抗着这个世界
That's right. It's James against the world.
你一直感觉这么孤立无援吗
Have you always felt singled out like this?
你这是赤裸裸的嫉妒
You are so jealous!
以为我不知道你对萨姆的想法吗
You think I don't know how you feel about Sam? Huh?
你应该在工作之余
You should go to church more often,
多去去教堂
outside of office hours, James.
我要是在附近
If I find one more of these things
再看到一次这东西
around the neighborhood,
你就要下岗了
you will lose your job!
试试看怎么在萧条时期找个工作吧 鲍勃
Try and find a new job in this economy, Bob.
作为一个曾经失明的人 我告诉你这可不容易
As a former blind man, I can tell you it's not easy.
"但他从没买过彩票"
"But he's never bought a lottery ticket."
我看着你们 这么多张不同的脸
Now, I look into this crowd, and I see different faces.
有老人
I see old men and women.
年轻夫妇
I see young couples.
单亲母亲
Single mothers.
年轻男人 一个个家庭
I see young men. Whole families!
为什么你们都到这里来
But why are you all here?
为什么你们都在这
Why are you all here?
因为你们的沉溺
It's because of your addiction.
沉溺于债务
Your addiction to debt.
沉溺于债务经济
To the economy of debt.
从来不接那个陌生号码
To never picking up when that unlisted number
打来的电话
flashes on your phone.
一睁开眼就躲避催债电话
To waking up in the morning and dodging phone calls.
和银行账单
And red letters.
我们都有这些问题
I mean, we all have these problems, right?
那为何我们还理所当然地超前消费
Then, why do we feel it right to live beyond our means?
为何要过入不敷出的生活
Why should we live beyond our earnings?
十五年来 我们被牢牢困住
What sense does it make when we're stuck,
债务缠身
15 years down the line,
这么做意义何在
shackled with debt?
债务压得我们喘不过气
Debt hanging down our throats.
银行在乎你生活艰难吗
Does the bank care about your hard life?
不
No.
在乎你收入低下吗
Do... do they care about your low income?
不 不
No. No.
他们不在乎
They don't.
不好意思
Excuse me!
不好意思 先生
Excuse me, sir.
我卖掉房子的话 最快多久能拿到钱
How soon can I get the money, once I sell the house?
你会立刻收到一张支票
Well, you'll get a check right away.
现金呢
Cash?
你可以把支票兑现
Well, you can cash that check. Yeah.
也许你应该再考虑考虑 这是个重大决定
Maybe you should think about it, you know? It's a big decision.
嗯...我知道 我只是...
I... I realize that, I just...
有没有办法
Is there, um, any way to move
能优先处理我这一单
to the front of the line with this?
这是我的名片
Take my card, and, um...
我希望你再三思一下
I want you to think about it... More.
好吗
You promise?
如果你决定好了
And if you're still sure, uh...
给我打电话
give me a call.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
妈妈最近怎么样
How's mom?
挺好的
She's fine.
疯狂运动
She's... going crazy with the exercising.
现在是个健身狂魔
She's like a complete gym freak now.
是啊 她一直喜欢尝试新鲜事物
Yeah, she's always liked getting into new stuff.
嘿 爸爸
Hey, dad.
我觉得这挺好的
I think it's good, 'cause...
因为锻炼能产生胺多酚
Exercise creates endorphins.
- 我觉得对她有好处 - 是啊
- I think that's really good for her. - Yeah.
她还会去跳舞
She goes dancing, too.
哦是吗
Oh yeah?
在SVI
At the svi?
哦 和谁
Oh, who with?
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Oh, nothing.
我失去吸引力了吗
I'm losing my novelty?
不是
No.
不是的
It's not that.
情况总是如此的
It's always that.
我觉得乔纳交了女朋友
I think Jonah's got a girlfriend now.
他说他不想留在这了
And he says he doesn't want to stay here.
这需要点时间
It's gonna take time.
我知道
I know.
我九岁时 我爸爸就去世了
My dad left when I was nine.
慢慢就习惯了
You get used to it.
我觉得我爸妈待在一起
I think my parents stayed together
只是因为我视力不断衰退
just 'cause I was going blind.
那时我每晚都听到爸爸祷告
I used to hear my dad praying every night
祈祷我的视力不要再变差
for my vision not to get any worse.
他还在世吗
Is... is he still alive?
不在了
No.
那对他来说非常重要
It was so important to him.
你知道吗 我还常常...
You know, I used to...
说谎骗他
lie about it.
我告诉他我还看得见 其实我已经看不见了
I used to tell him I could still see things when I couldn't.
他比我还难接受这件事
He took it way harder than I ever did.
她从没让我做自己想成为的人
She never let me be who I wanted.
没有人在评判你
Nobody's judging you.
也许上帝会
Maybe god is.
上帝没那么闲呢
Mmm. God has better things to do.
你不信上帝吗
You don't believe in god?
在... 时运不济时
Oh, when... things are bad.
需要信仰时 我才信
When I need to believe, I believe.
那就不是信仰
That's not what belief is.
那么 我不信
Well, then, I don't believe.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
来给你送支票
Just gonna give you the check.
寄过来就好了
You could've just mailed it.
你现在跑步了
You're running now?
- 对 - 你气色很好
- Yeah. - You look good.
为了新认识的男士们
Yeah. Gotta stay in shape
得保持好身材嘛
for all the handsome new men in my life.
我就是来看看你好不好
Just came to see how you were doing.
谢谢你的探望
Thanks for coming by.
我有点担心...
You know, I'm a little worried about, uh...
乔纳
about Jonah.
为什么
Why?
我不知道 他好像... 好像不一样了
I don't know, he seems... he seems different.
有麻烦了吗
Any trouble?
麻烦
Troubles?
这叫滑板期
It's called, you know, going through a skater phase.
是成长的一个阶段
It's a part of growing up.
滑板期 我可能一直...
The skater phase, I guess, I never...
一直没看出来
never saw that.
还有他爸爸搬走一事的影响
Yeah, that and the whole thing with his father moving out.
房子看起来很好
House looks nice.
我得... 冲个淋浴
I'm gonna... get showered up.
先进去了...
Head inside so...
我能进去吗
Can I come in?
不行
No.
爸爸...
Dad...
怎么了
What's wrong?
乔纳
Hey, Jonah.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
我从没注意到这房子在夜里会发光
I never noticed how this house glows at night.
从街那头都看得到
You can see it from down the street.
我... 我得回去了
I... I have to get back inside.
妈妈去跳舞了
Mom's at the dance.
那天晚上 然后我要去厕所
that night. And I had to go the bathroom.
一会再说吧
Maybe later, though.
鲍勃 鲍詹姆斯来了
Bob, Bob, James is here.
我不要
I'm not going to do it.
给我们一分钟 好吗
Just give us a minute, okay?
天啊 跟我说 没事的
Oh, god. Tell me it's okay.
好的
All right.
谢谢
Thanks.
我曾以为我来这里是为了你
You know, I used to think I came here for you.
其实不是
That's not true.
我是为自己而来的
I came here for me.
这结局真是滑稽 你不觉得吗
Funny how everything works out in the end, don't you think?
我放手了 你却出现在这里
Me moving on and you showing up here.
鲍勃舞跳得很好
Bob's a good dancer.
别担心 我们只是跳舞
Don't worry, we're just dancing.
我不会夺走你唯一的朋友
I wouldn't take your only friend.
你应该找个时间带她过来
You should bring her here sometime.
她可能会喜欢
She might like it.
可以陪我跳支舞吗
Can I have this dance?
一切看起来都正常
Everything looks normal.
记者又来电话了
That reporter called again.
她想要什么
What does she want?
要跟负责人谈谈
To speak to somebody in charge.
你不该接这种电话 公共关系部
You shouldn't be taking those calls. P.R.
你看起来有点不舒服
You're not doing too good.
不
No.
现在不行 现在不行
Not now. Not now.
现在不行 拜托
Not now. Please.
不
No.
我们为你暖气装置中
We're adding a $104 credit
剩下的油多付104美元
for the oil left in your heating.
好的
That would be fine.
那么 都齐了
Here we are, then.
这是卖契 都填好了
Here's the deed of sale, all filled out.
207号的排屋房产
For the townhouse at the 207 property.
看起来没问题
This looks right.
请在这里签字
We just need you to sign here.
我对我的生活和经历
I am deeply satisfied with my life
很满足
and everything in it.
我为今天而活 我享受每一天
I live for today, and I enjoy what I do.
我不与他人攀比
I do not compare myself to others.
我感恩自己拥有的一切
I'm thankful for everything I have.
我对我的生活和经历
I am deeply satisfied with my life...
很满足
and everything in it.
我为今天而活 我享受每一天
I live for today, and I enjoy what I do.
我不与他人攀比
I do not compare myself to others.
你打算什么时候才告诉我
When were you going to tell me?
你以为别人注意不到吗
Do you think people won't notice?
你打算怎么办
What are you going to do?
保密 假装你还能看见吗
Keep it a secret? Pretend you can see?
我会处理的
I can take care of this.
我可以帮你
I can help you.
我不需要你帮忙
I don't need your help.
不 你需要
Yes, you do.
我自己能解决
I can fix this.
怎么解决
How?
詹姆斯 让我帮你吧
James, let me help you.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
谢谢你们的捧场
Thank you all for being here.
有个人向上帝祈祷了...
A man prays to god...
五十年
for 50 years.
每晚都是同样的祷告
The same prayer, every night.
"上帝 求你让我中彩票吧"
"God, please let me win the lottery."
夜复一夜
Every single night.
年复一年
Year after year.
"求你了 上帝...
"Please, god...
让我中彩票吧"
let me win the lottery."
终于有一位天使去问上帝
And finally an angel goes to god,
他说
and he says,
"上帝 这个人已经祈祷了这么久
"God, this man has been praying so long.
你为什么不让他中奖呢"
Why don't you let him win?"
上帝说 "我很想帮他
And god says, "I'd love to help him,
但他从来都...
but he's never bought...
没买过彩票啊"
a lottery ticket."
我看着你们 看到了不同的面孔
I look into this crowd, and I see different faces.
有老人
I see old men and women.
年轻夫妇
I see young couples.
一家人
I see whole families.
你们为什么来到这里
Now, why are you all here?
你们为什么在这里
Why are you all here?
我曾活得像你们一样
I used to live like you.
我曾活得像你们一样 债务缠身
I used to live like you. I was saddled with debt.
而现在...
And now...
浪费时间
Waste of time.
而现在... 不同了
And I'm not... anymore.
我跟迪克森谈过了
I talked to Dixon.
他可以接手你的工作
He can take your responsibilities.
减轻你的负担
Ease off the load.
我感恩我拥有的一切
I'm thankful for everything I have.
我对我的生活和经历很满足
Deeply satisfied with my life and everything in it.
我为今天而活 我享受每一天
I live for today, and I enjoy what I do.
我不与他人攀比
I do not compare myself to others.
我感恩我拥有的一切
I'm thankful for what I have.
我对我的生活和经历很满足
I'm deeply satisfied with my life and everything in it.
我为今天而活 我享受每一天
I live for the moment. I enjoy what I do.
我不与他人攀比 上帝 上帝啊
I do not compare myself to others. Oh, god, god, god.
上帝... 上帝 原谅... 上帝啊
God... god, forgive... oh, god!
上帝 求你了
Please, god.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
求你了 上帝 求你了
Please, god! Please, god!
求你... 求求你了 上帝
Please... please. Please, god.
我完了
I'm fucked!
上帝啊
Oh, god!
求你了 求你了 上帝
Please, god. Please, god. Please, god!
上帝啊
Oh, god!
求你了 上帝 求求你 帮帮我
Please, god. Please, help me.
求你了 上帝
Please, god. Please!
求你了 对不起
Please. I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
求你了 对不起
Please, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 求你了
I'm sorry, please.
求你了 上帝
Please, god.
求求你 对不起
Please, I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起 原谅我 原谅我
I'm sorry. Forgive me. Forgive me.
求求你了 上帝
Please, god, please!
求你了 求你了 求你了
Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
上帝啊
Oh, god! Oh, god!
求你了 上帝 求你了
Please, god! Please! Please!
上帝 上帝啊
Oh, god. Oh, god!
鲍勃
Bob!
鲍勃 你在吗
Bob, are you there?
鲍勃 我知道你在
Bob, I know you're there.
鲍勃 拜托
Bob, please!
把门打开吧 鲍勃
Please open up, Bob!
鲍勃
Bob?
鲍勃 拜托
Bob, please.
鲍勃
Bob?
鲍勃 求你了
Bob, please.
你拥有我想要的一切
You have everything I want.
我想要的一切
Everything I ever wanted.
但你搞砸了
And you messed it up!
鲍勃
Bob?
你以为她还会要你吗
What, you think she's gonna take you back now?
天啊
God!
你是个坏人
You're no good.
你觉得你配得上她吗
You think she deserves you?
她还维护你呢
You know, she still protects you?
她还理解你
She still understands you.
你干嘛不爬回去找她
So, won't you crawl on back to her.
爬回家去
Crawl on home.
从我家滚出去
Get the hell out of my house.
滚
Get out!
天啊
My god.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
- 詹姆斯 - 对不起
- James? - I'm sorry.
要不要我给医生打电话
Do you need me to call a doctor?
- 你... - 不 不用
- Are you...? - No, no.
不用
No.
你真好闻
You smell so good.
你不能这样对我
You can't do this to me.
我不能重新接受你
I can't take you back.
你知道的
You know that.
嘘...
Shh...
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.com
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub